One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's knock them into next week, Kaido.
How many of those five
do you think will survive?
Trafalgar!
Can't you move one of them
downstairs with your ability?
If I could, I would've done it already.
Their haki's too strong. I can't move them!
In that case, let's disassemble 'em.
Hey! Here comes a big one!
Hope your hips still work, you old hag!
Who do you think
you're talking to, smart aleck?!
– Conquest of the Sea!
You've gotta be kidding me!
No way! We can't dodge that!
Get outta here, guys!
If they keep this up...
we're all done for!
Zoro!
I can't see them,
but I can still hear them...
They must've escaped. Color me impressed.
Zoro, are you alive?
I think so...
Nice work blocking it for as long as you did.
Thanks.
Where's Straw Hat?
Kaido!
Gum-Gum...
Red...
Why'd you dodge, Kaido?!
Was it gonna hurt?!
Ow, ow, ow...
Extend your hand, no need to fear
Cut through the wind, and persevere
Chart your own course, the time to push forward is here
In a time like a storm, hear the tidal waves roar,
we keep trudging along but we're still wanting more
But in spite of it all, the foundation we built
for ourselves was about to fall
Where the compass points - Is it right? Is it wrong?
Who to ask? As if there's anyone listening
I guess you'll never be one hundred percent sure
But if you shut your eyes to the chaos,
and you'd only take a breath
When you open up your eyes
you will find where you were meant to be
Extend your hand, no need to fear
Cut through the wind, and persevere
Kick out the dark until the sky clears
Even as we act in our own best interests,
doing what we each believe is for our own
Chart your own course, the time to push forward is here
Conqueror's Haki
Excellent! Burn!
Let the flames rise!
Dammit! They won't go down!
We have enough problems as it is!
Fukurokuju! You know where they keep
all those explosives, don't you?!
Indeed. Allow me to show you the way.
Everything is ablaze! What is going on?!
Go to hell, Kaido!
And take your
New Onigashima Project with you!
Orochi!
This was all your doing?!
Ah, so you finally show your faces!
The half-ghost vermin of the Kozuki!
What are you even here for?!
For twenty years,
you've gone to hell and back,
and now you've followed me all the way here!
Is that how much you hate me?
How much you resent me?!
Lord Orochi...
They are not aware that you've died once.
Please make your escape.
I shall dispose of–
Butt out, you simpleton!
You're covered in cuts and bruises...
No wonder!
You ran willingly to your own deaths!
You guys must be completely
out of your minds!
Orochi! We have no time
to waste on a fool like you.
Move!
And if I refuse?
What?!
Do you have any idea
just who it is you're defying?!
Know your place, rodents!
I am the shogun of Wano!
What's with that look?!
I've done nothing wrong!
All I did was take revenge on
the Kozuki as they rightly deserved!
I only took back
what was stolen from me!
But you oafs just don't get it!
Citizens and samurai alike are meant to
bow before and obey their shogun!
I'm the one with the power here!
Flower Shuriken!
It's all because this country oppressed me!
Th-That look in your eyes!
Are you trying to tell me that I'm wrong?!
Don't look at me...
Don't look at me!
I can't be wrong!
Stop looking at me like that!
Lord Orochi!
Your punishment will be decided in hell.
Onward!
Will you avenge your lord?
I thought too little of you, Fukurokuju.
Foolish as he was, you remained
loyal until the bitter end.
I could say the same to all of you!
Even had I not sought vengeance,
you and I would be destined to fight!
I'm sure you understand, Raizo!
Indeed!
Let's do this!
You asked for it, whelp!
Not gonna happen!
Come all at once for all I care!
Give it to him good!
You shithead!
Thanks!
Kaido!
Conqueror of Three Worlds...
Ragnaraka!
Luffy!
Let's mop up the leftovers, too!
It's ready!
Okay!
Room!
Shambles!
Where am I?! It's so dark!
Zeus!
You got this, Roronoa?!
I'd better!
You're not getting back to her!
Flame-Rend: Crossing the Six Paths!
Quit it! Come on, I'm just a sword!
– Mama, help!
You guys!
Now!
Punk Pistols!
What now?!
You actually thought tearing us apart
would be enough to beat us?!
Repel!
Takt!
You nitwit!
You think a rock is enough to finish me?!
Die!
Crap!
Mama!
If she can't get help, then that's one down!
How do you like that?!
Come help me!
Zeus!
Mama!
What's going on, Mama?!
Mama! I'm coming to–
Mama! I'm gonna–
That moron...
I wouldn't be surprised if he shattered
every bone in his body back there!
That was pathetic, Linlin!
I have to do everything myself.
Hey, Pirate Hunter!
Release Prometheus!
Shambles!
Injection Shot!
You've got one hell of a strange ability!
Trafalgar!
Curtain!
Mama!
Stay away!
Hey, Traffy!
Fire-face there...
is gonna save Big Mom!
Just let him go...
I'd rather the mission be a failure...
than have one of us die.
All we wanted to do was
separate Big Mom and Kaido!
No need to put your life on the line!
Leave Big Mom to me!
That was close!
I'm glad you're safe, Mama!
Aren't you just the sweetest?
Prometheus!
Unlike somebody...
What the hell is Zeus doing?!
Useless little airhead!
I...
couldn't agree more, Mama!
He's such a klutz, always lagging behind.
You said it!
Hey, so, I got a favor to ask, Mama!
What is it?
Look at Straw Hat's face!
It's just like last time.
He's out cold, and yet...
he's still glaring at me!
Should those eyes...
be the first things I crush?
Or maybe...
his brain?
Or even his heart?!
Traffy.
What I'm about to do...
will push me to the limit.
Zoro?!
Dragging things out here...
is only wearing us down.
And if this doesn't work...
then it's just our time to die.
After this...
it's all you.
Hey, Kaido!
That's our captain!
Why don't you try...
crushing my head first?!
Demonic Nine-Sword Style!
Asura!
Blades Drawn!
Nine-Sword Style!
ASURA
BLADES
DRAWN
Asura: Blades Drawn...
DEAD MAN'S
GAME
Dead Man's Game!
Damn!
This kid...
Don't tell me...
you've got conqueror's haki, too?!
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you mean.
That was... my ultimate attack!
Would've been nice...
if you'd at least fallen down...
You've done plenty.
This scar will remain.
This generation, I tell you...
Hey! Zoro, run!
Don't trouble yourself.
I'll just come to you.
Thunder Bagua!
What a shame...
If you'd just come with me,
we could've achieved world domination...
With you?
We'd never join up with you, idiot.
We love samurai.
I'm gonna kick your ass, end of story!
You're...
gonna kick my ass, huh?
Give it your best shot.
As if your reckless fists...
would ever be good enough!
Don't strain yourself!
It's a powerful force that is both
an invisible armor and a tool for offense.
However, if you advance to the next level,
the haki that covers you
will become even stronger,
reaching inside your opponents
and destroying them from within.
Don't strain yourself!
Allow the unused haki in
your body to flow to your fist!
Kong Gun!
It was still too shallow.
Power blooms in our darkest hour!
But after taking that hit
from your club, I figured it out.
You can infuse things with
conqueror's haki, can't you?
How will knowing that help you?
Think you can do it?!
Only the strongest...
can wield it like that!
You half-ghost rat!
Don't strain yourself!
Allow the unused haki in
your body to flow to your fist!
He didn't even touch him!
Zoro...
Traffy...
Thanks for watching my back.
Now head downstairs!
No matter what else happens,
I'm taking him down!
So go on...
and let everyone know!